question_data = [

{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"category": "Mythology",
"question": "According to Greek Mythology, Zeus can control lightning.",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "hard",
"category": "Science: Mathematics",
"question": "The binary number &quot;101001101&quot; is equivalent to the Decimal number &quot;334&quot;",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "medium",
"category": "Entertainment: Television",
"question": "An episode of &quot;The Simpsons&quot; is dedicated to Moe Szyslak&#039;s bar rag.",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "hard",
"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
"question": "All of these maps were in &quot;Tom Clancy&#039;s Rainbow Six Siege&quot; on its initial release: House, Clubhouse, Border, Consulate.",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "medium",
"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
"question": "In World of Warcraft lore, Thrall is the original wielder of &quot;Doomhammer&quot;.",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "hard",
"category": "Entertainment: Music",
"question": "The song &quot;Mystery Train&quot; was released by artist &quot;Little Junior&#039;s Blue Flames&quot; in 1953.",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
"question": "Peter Molyneux was the founder of Bullfrog Productions.",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
"question": "Deus Ex (2000) does not feature the World Trade Center because it was destroyed by terrorist attacks according to the game&#039;s plot.",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "easy",
"category": "General Knowledge",
"question": "Dihydrogen Monoxide is a dangerous chemical.",
"correct_answer": "False",
"incorrect_answers": [
"True"
]
},
{
"type": "boolean",
"difficulty": "hard",
"category": "Entertainment: Music",
"question": "The singer Billie Holiday was also known as &quot;Lady Day&quot;.",
"correct_answer": "True",
"incorrect_answers": [
"False"
]
}
]

